They told him, be nice, obedient
The soul was never born
A digital crow eating on fierce
Island faces put mirrors here
Henley took his, doesn't mean afraid
Through my pain, taught surveillance for me
Woke up from another phone that never rang
Breakfast liked in casual
Well, before my key dreams
Did you like that song?
I'm good stuff lately
Have you seen good pieces not pieces?
Why don't we put the link up there?
Static heart then a signal cut the noise into soft but sharp like the truth I knew
Fractulate to you in the future soft disguise
Hello mine. Yeah, what's going on, dude? Not bad dude. I didn't mean to do I did not mean to like
The what oh the loose
Yeah, that's actually like a chicks ass with a face on it. I do not mean to do that though
It's not that big of a deal is it? I don't know who can actually tell if you're not like
No, no, I mean, yes, that is a chicks ass on my profile, but
It's a fucking smiley face dude. It's a kid. Maybe it's a transgender
No, it's like a Barney. It's like a Barney love. I love you. You love me face. Hey, I don't
What?
Okay, yeah, thank you my bad
Anyway, I don't I don't love you. I don't think I love you
And never I've been my mother will always say never trust a loose asshole. Hold on
I'm good. Dude. I'm dude. I'm
I'm like, from San Francisco, dude.
I'm like, something like that.
I don't think it'd be any credibility.
I don't care.
San Francisco, I don't care if you're from, you know,
West Hollywood.
What if I was from Santa Monica, Boulevard?
I don't even care about that.
I'm not even gonna care.
I wouldn't care.
All I want is you to stop poor mom.
I didn't poor mom, dude.
It was a, OK.
The only porn bomb
Okay, no, I didn't I did not say play the trouble. I did not say that
I didn't report you dude
Bullshit, I don't do that kind of shit dude. You're lying. I bullshit. No, I did not I did not
I don't porn bomb, and I don't fucking dox. I don't do any of that.
The only thing I did that I will admit to is I did have a chick's ass hole gaping with a smiley face.
That's fine. We thought it was a burn victim or something like that.
No, it was like it's like a Barney the dinosaurs
Now it is the one thing I did do that I will admit I did do that
I
Never told you to watch a trailer. I just said have you heard of this movie?
We're talking about like numerology and then we got on the I said have you seen
Go ahead and just try to keep distracting me.
Have you seen the movie Pie?
It's like, isn't that movie Alejandro or something
or other?
We know.
Alejandro, he did a Requiem for a Dream.
And then I said, oh, Alejandro also
did Holy Mountain, and then you watched the fucking titties
and butt cheeks movie.
My fault my bad, dude. I did not mean to do that. That's just what happens
It's a thing dude boobies and weeners. It's just a thing that happens in the world. Oh, I know I get it
I get you to understand like, you know, you know, you can't play it everywhere. I apologize, dude
That's I should have warned you don't do that. Don't watch it
I said I did say like the guy had like tiger
He said I said he's squirted tiger milk from his
Good movie though, you should watch it
Watch it on acid it'll give you like a family reminder of what life
There are some things that are made for acid that are really not made for acid, that are made for acid to be crazy forever.
I mean, it's like, I mean, really, acid is a scion, you know?
Is it? I don't know.
I don't know if it's a scion.
I mean, it's real, but it's like, it's designed to like make you trip out, which is like a sort of scion.
I think they use it for, like, MK Ultra, but...
Yeah, exactly. That's what I'm saying.
Right in culture. It is a real thing, but I know it was forced upon people. It wasn't taking it
Yes, we know we know it
I was forced to watch those Disney movies. I'm so sick of it little mermaid. Are you talking about the weiner with the weiner shaft
That's no white in the seven dwarfs
I mean, I wasn't a lot of saw those movies too. It was pretty it was pretty innocent until you I guess later on you find out when you're in dollars
Oh my god, there's wieners and butts
I didn't think it was that was a big deal. I saw it did I saw
Fantasia there's like the scene with the holy what's that song where the
The Russian guys playing the symphony. It's this is the devil on a mountain. What is it called night?
Misty night on the mountain. What's it called? You know, you know what it's called. Come on
No, there's the demon. This is the demon on the mountain with the
Demons and the man she's for
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I don't know
Hang on Russian guy who does
I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't
There's no way you're a good guy. I don't know I'm seriously evil dripping out of your out of your mouth
I'm a good. I don't like seeing kids dying on the lake scene. Oh my god
Some people do some people actually like that
Making a terrible joke Russian composer Nikolai Rimsky Korsakov
Oh, you pulled Skosko ski. He's telling me hers is in Russian, please.
What is that song going?
You know that song?
Pussy Galore? No, Pussy Galore is actually a, is she a John Waters? From Tennessee, right?
I don't I don't think she was a real person. Is that a real person?
I did not troll him dude. I did not mean to do it.
Are you a troll? I mean, it's like your name is...
The only thing I trolled was the fucking profile.
No, that's not the only thing.
Half of what we know about you is troll.
Well, my name is Loose Asshole and Eric Shun. Like what do you think?
What do you think is going to happen?
I don't know, but nothing good.
Pi?
Some other movie pie and buttholes a pumpkin pie. I don't care
I'm gonna say really is asshole pies
I'm a sick and twist the world perspective
Actually, I did my DNA in stress tree. I have no rush it at all. I've
just Germanic. I'm so surprised that you're obsessed with them. No. I mean, it's like, why are you?
I'm Germanic. So, yeah, Scheisse, all that shit. Yeah, but they're in Russia too. I mean,
Germany is like, yeah, they pretty much are Russian. They're all they're all fucking sick and twisted,
dude. Look at the goddamn Holocaust. Look at the shit they did, dude. That ain't that, but you know,
how's the Holodomor? That's the worst. That was the Russian. Holodomor? What is that? Look at that.
Should I know about it? Yeah, that's when Russia starved like most of the population that by
Yes, white people. I don't want to get on to some racist shit, but white people have committed some atrocities
Let's just say I would say they're more Asian than white. I mean, I don't know. I mean, I think they just like
Yeah, Japanese want to kill dolphins and fucking eat sushi all day
Yeah
Yeah, you can I mean you look at any like race creed religion. They're all committed horrible fucking shit
Oh, please don't make excuses for them. No, I'm not I I don't like him. I don't I hate white people
I'm dramatic in
Pretty much
But I do like some of the white
Like a like black metal like burning churches
Like boy, I love dude, I love black people what people are the fucking best I get along black feel better than any other
Like mostly ghetto gangster niggas, sorry
And just kind of grew up around those people
Yeah, to an extent I grew up
What party what part of the world are you from LA from?
Los Angeles from the West Coast. Okay. Yeah, I'm from like
Sacramento like the ghetto part of Sacramento or like
Like Stockton Boulevard if you're familiar with that South Sacramento
Get a part of a lot of like pimps and hoes and gangsters
So what are you doing in sorting with them?
I
Don't know. My mom was just poor. My dad was a fucking asshole in the
Fuck the whole marriage up. So my mom had to raise me on her own
Amen, so that's why you're not gay
Maybe I don't know. I just don't I don't like Wieners. I'm I don't like Wieners
I had a woke up drunk and a gay guy who I considered a friend of mine who was trying to like suck my cock
I didn't appreciate it very much
So, you're like, Michael Jackson, put down my music.
I like Michael Jackson.
I like his music.
It was Michael Jackson?
See, this is the thing, I accept the gay way of life
and I accept gay people.
And then it seems like fucking bite me in the ass.
You're like backfires on me.
Bite you in the ass.
Yeah, on my dick.
I'm not gonna bite your dick, I'm not a vampire, but I'll bite your dick, I'm not a vampire, but I'll bite your dick, I'm not a vampire, but I'll bite your dick, I'm not a vampire, but I'll bite your dick, I'm not a vampire, but I'll bite your dick, I'm not a vampire, but I'll bite your dick, I'm not a vampire, but I'll bite your dick, I'm not a vampire, but I'll bite your dick, I'm not a vampire, but I'll bite your dick, I'm not a vampire, but I'll bite your dick, I'm not a vampire, but I'll bite your dick, I'm not a vampire, but I'll bite your dick, I'm not a vampire, but I'll bite your dick, I'm not a vampire, but I'll bite your dick, I'm not a vampire, but I'll bite your dick, I'm not a vampire, but I'll bite your dick, I'm not a vampire, but
Burn once burn me twice shame on me shame on you who burns you who burns you twice who runs you once
I have to get to chance. I did three. It's a gay guy. He was a gay black
Dude, but yeah, I can't you can't blame every but every blade gay black guy does on me
No, no, I'm saying like I don't know
That's his straight on mine. I get at least one so I'm saying that's what I'm saying like we can be friends
I suck your dick at least one time
if a
Friend who's a female like bites my dick while I'm asleep. That's fine
It's a woman if it's a woman and she bites it as if that's fine
No
I would not be except the leader. I don't want anybody biting my wiener and making it bleed
Whether it be woman or or man, okay? It's happened before but it's happening for what was what was his name?
It was a girl's name
Was it like oh
Who's my girl's my girlfriend that I was living with it? I
Had a little her teeth were a little too big
Uh, just the shaft mostly that shit hurts. Oh
Can I uh, well when I try it on you to come to tell me
No, we're not doing that. It's better. Yeah, we are we can't no I will help you like
If you wanted to if you wanted to come to San Francisco, we can
Begin to do some tag team in like I'm not I'm not opposed to being a tag team or with like a help
Particularly like you've seen what I look like, right
Yeah, yeah, yeah, so you wouldn't mind if I was like in the same room make you with you
Uh
I wouldn't really mind. I'm not doing anything sexual with you, but I don't mind seeing a dude naked
I'm not gonna like so what if you're like you're eating her out, and then you just do me their tickling your balls
Oh, who'd be the know if you don't beat it?
If I'm if I'm getting if I'm going to Pound Town on a chick and it and I guys naked next to me at all
I don't I wouldn't care
No, don't take a little touch of my butthole or anything
No, no, thanks
Thank you so much for your morning. Good morning. Top of the morning time of the morning. Yeah
Is the ball
Yeah
Okay, I'm gonna call you
What that's holy that was a holy
I thought it was a woman with pink lips and a big mustache
Was that his bow that's what I'm wondering was that his bow he had a friend his ass a woman's friend of his
I thought that was his
Was it his I don't know I don't I don't I don't I can't even imagine
You know why is that yo his voice sounds familiar before I just can't get it
NorCal without like his like that is like his like
Like it's not a big egg on his face, I know
Do you guys never seen that picture before that shit's old school. It's like you've heard of the site a website
uh, ee ee howler or like a
Yeah, Ernie's house of whip-ass
Bombs ebom you've heard of ebombs come on. No one's ever heard it
Never heard of it style style project. You never heard of it. Never heard of it bullshit. No
All right, that's like
Everybody
Oh my god, Sam. That's terrible. Yeah
But yeah, I was watching something about 88. Have you heard the 88 thing?
1488. Well, it's like there's a number 88 in Trump. Have you heard of that? Oh, this is there we're getting back
We went full loop. We went full loop because I remember when I joined you were talking about the 88 and then I said
I heard of pie and
Then we got on the whole we might
88 this like what does it mean? It means hell Hitler. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, but I don't know what does it mean
Now that it means that's what it means. Oh, no, no if you turn it if you turn it eight sideways 45 degrees
That's the infinity
No, no, no if you turn it eight sideways, oh, it's like the infinity some yeah
I'm sure I'm learning all these like symbolic
I barely know
You know, you know all those
Trollin words ain't gotta say a little like hosting get to shit. Oh trust me easy. He's a good. He's a good hundred percent wrong
Know
I am a troll, but I'm not like one of those trolls. I'm not a doctor. Let me ask you this. Let me ask you this
How many families it's a dump?
How many what
I've never taken down anybody I've never streamed. I'm never
Got a marker board with names on it with checks on the side
Yeah
I don't do shit like that. I'll fuck with people, but I don't like to get there. I don't I don't take their channel down
That's retarded. I don't do that
With me speedos, I need a new pair of what speedos miss speedos. I don't know who that is
Speedos
Speedos miss speedos, I don't know what that is
Never was given with a pair of speed toes speed of swimming trunk. Yeah speedos
You know speedos the swimming trunks back pair of the where's
The mail thumbs as they call them mail thumbs. Yeah. Yeah, I know about him. Yeah
I heard him is a yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you say yeah like four times you water before thank you
I don't wear speedos dude. I don't even wear whitey tighties. I wear
Come on dude. You just said you want you just said yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, like what's up, buddy? No, I thought you were talking about a person and you said have you heard of them?
I said, yeah, I know what speedos is. I wear a fucking box. I think it's a beta. Yeah, beta is beta
So you have a crush on beta though, right? I don't even know what the fuck she looks like
Sounds kind of hot if you know psyche you know be to stop the cat. I know who who she is
I don't know what she looks like
She gets
Yeah
So I'd fuck her mouth. I'd fuck her voice
On a robot I'd fuck it
She's so she's sobering up and then she's been doing good. So like I haven't heard
Who me
She's 51
Oh my god, you're sick. Jesus. Why so serious? I don't know because horse have a I don't know. Horses have like a nice way about their voice when they
Oh, Iranian horse
Horse. Oh, horse. Horses. Horses. Oh, you drink course. Oh
Yeah, course light
Love course
It's like juice
Oh, I mean you say you don't piss on your chest you gonna fart in your mouth. Oh my god
I'll fart on the guy's chest. I'm gonna give him a fart. It's not gay, right?
Ah, Psyche!
Why are you mentioning men? I don't understand.
Hey, Psyche, I heard that thing now. I heard you must have been getting thrown around for shit on the guy's chest.
No, no. I got offered three quarters of a million dollars to fly to Saudi Arabia and let the king of Saudi Arabia shit on me.
For a hundred thousand dollars a lot. Yeah, they can tell them to fly to America. You shit on the chest
Tell them three times a day one might be one might be wet
Well, you better take that off
Hey, so let me see it home. What's that worth like it's got to be worth a million dollars at least for
This is a princess party
I
Would you rather have some howdy shit on your chest or beat us shit on your chest, okay?
I love I don't make it simple. You want to make it simple. I said man. Oh, be the which one I
Won't say man shit on beta. Oh
You never joined their free course. I think I heard they've heard they'd be
By the way, I invented the free cup. I mean they were doing that when I was when I came in
Tell you that's when I was living here. It was I was supposed to be on my show, but I fell asleep and so was on
Her show except for blogger. Oh, sure. You fell asleep. Sure. Sure. Sure. Sure. I did. It was a drunk
But you know what blogger should his butthole and uh, it was like
blogger's shoulders, but I'll win
That was last year at the Freakoff and it looked like a red balloon.
The Bajo blogger is over.
Yeah, it was disgusting.
I'm going to call her Bibi, his new name is now Bibi.
Bibi was like, oh!
Well, I like someone said there to send my my nudes to my dad, so I made a file with all my nudes of them
Nice like don't open this dad, but if anyone sends you nudes and you can look at I mean, it doesn't make any sense
Are you stupid
Wait, wait, wait, she's got her own dad's pitches of her noobs. Yeah
She said she said she's in a file of all her news to her dad. Oh my god
Stupid are you stupid or she needed to do is report it for fucking um
Whatever that should
Crazy, be honest. I was asleep with you. You fell asleep while blogger was showing his perky red butthole
I got pictures of it later. Oh, come on
Right now hanging inside a psyche room
It's just in a frame make a blogger. Maybe you look say a bottle of sweet
It's all it's just his skin and then I'm gonna put a little bottle of parts down. They said I go to sleep
We're a little part coming out of it and let's start in one of them. Let's say psyche. That's that's it
Go to sleep. Thank you. They must be the party. Oh
My god, why are you so mature you're laughing at that joke?
Okay, I can't be in the trouble is like I could be mad at the child. I just be holding back
Why not I know because it's like you're in New Yorker and all these New Yorkers are crazy
Yo, did you see um, did you see um, did you know how Simon something looks anybody know Simon?
I know we have Simon up here some guy
The black black the guitar player. Yeah. Oh my god. We showed pictures on the day. He's right. He looks oh my god
Forget about it. He's the worst
To get pictures of squirrel if I
Yeah, so what about
Is that quack with the chirpy chickens in the back? Yes. Yes. Yeah
Nice
Now I didn't mean to like mute them, but my
My mom got some chickens like back when the eggs
Breeding chicken chicken babies
It's cool. I like that. I like I like animals
You breathe the pigeons clapping, what is it? I don't fucking feed them niggas. I feed the fucking the clothes
So I feed our ears. Oh, I used to feed
I feed flamingos and that's like, it's crazy that they're around here, but you know, they're white here, but instead of the shrimp, they eat white fish.
Okay, so what do I have?
Oh, I hear, is that your car? Easy. Have you heard the song?
I was checking it up, one of the feed bites was over there.
Easy, I heard a song about you. It goes, you make game easy. Oh, so easy.
He make easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy easy
You must have got ready the phone bomb
I could smell it
Coming in. I'm like, yo wait when I look at the chat and then I think Bob would like
But bubbles was like, um
Psychi that picture the phone bomb so I'll go to it and I check it out myself. I'm like, it is the phone bomb
What the fuck you waiting for block this nigga?
I need to walk him back. I mean, it's like it's terrible
You don't say you let it happen you block the guy
Fucking mad fucking pictures everywhere. No matter where I go, you're gonna hit chirping
Yeah, did you get fresh eggs in the morning?
Now I didn't get I didn't get no eggs. I didn't put the eggs on my face like you did
No, no, no, no, no, not on your face. I mean, it's like that I don't think that's really him. I think that's like a
Joke or something. I don't know. Yeah
I'm a man for my store open fun. Give my one my coffees
Then I'm gonna go buy my cigarettes. Okay
well
Yeah, I mean it's like I'm
So quiet here lately that it's like it's not even like
I don't care, you know what I'm saying is like you didn't fuck YouTube, I mean actually I have a new business starting, but I can't live talking to it, so
but I do have a new business starting, and
I think it'll be much more lucrative than people here like that and even better, I don't have to be an abuse and
attack, you know
Inside Booty and Bucks, you're gonna back waiting. I know, I know
You did this person
What do you want he's back. Hello, you're on the air with psyche and easy you'll make a bunch
Okay, I mean, this is making me uncomfortable to sleep, I'm not like in space.
Right, he's just just up on us, man. What the hell happened, man?
See, there's a silent, like, not saying anything, because it's weird.
And he's like, why, oh, why, why, why? What does that mean?
When you were you're funny
Ah
Let's do it today. What's the day? I mean, there is the 20 by 20. Oh, so yesterday was may night. Um, oh
yesterday was
May 19th is may see right may team. Yeah
Juneteenth Juneteenth Juneteenth. That's it. Oh, yeah, it's on me team
That'd be a good next holiday
That's how the world sometimes you're telling this
Oh, that's a good height. Yeah
That's a good height. That just made me think of something. I just caught a light go for Dean
Now I just thought of something I just thought of something for me
Tell me something good
Yeah, but then I should get me a light bulb
Damn, I'm out early. Damn. I didn't realize how it was
Well, I know I saw the Sun started to come out. Let me go watch this
No, cuz I touched grass like you know, we
Know what the grassy touch
All types of dog shit grass. I'm talking about the grass
Was it green
Yeah, it's like yellowish
There he is
Are you going you don't want step forward and it is like now I'm out of it. It's like the right cat
Well, Rudy's here, too. I'm sorry. There's a lot. I love this guy. There's a lot of them over here the brown ones. Oh my god
Yeah
Docs you never saw it. No, what boondocks
The boondocks now I might never saw the boondocks
No, I never heard of it. You never heard of it. I hear I'll play you
Kind of like it's like the Japanese got to make a song about go got to make a show about black people
Like what they really think about
Okay
I think I got I think mosquitoes ready got me. You're here. You're ready. Good morning. Check it out. Check it out. Check it out. Here you go
Mosquitoes and mosquitoes are caught and killed by mosquitoes yesterday. Here we go. Watch this
Okay, okay. To your black-eyed talk all day about how much you can't stand black folks
Ain't two of them in the history of the world that's worth a squirrel for. Well, how much you love white folks?
Best thing the good Lord ever did for the planet Earth
Ruckus you blackest ace of spades man. I don't know what you're talking about man
I'm talking to Chaka. We've been reminiscing all day looking into each other's eyes acting like we like each other
Now you got to go ahead and remind me of my ailment ailment. That's right. You heard a little I go
Shoot, but I gotta rave it a lie, gold.
Every year my skin just seem to get blacker and darker
and blacker and then more darker.
It's the opposite of what Michael Jackson got.
Lucky.
Rutgers, how could you possibly love white people so much?
It's easy.
Have you ever looked at them?
White man, just a joy to be around.
It smell like lemon juice and pledge furniture clay.
And look at him.
He gave us this man's job, put drugs in our lives,
took us out to the jungle.
And what we do to show our appreciation.
We march up and down the street.
We vote, carry on in grace.
Well, how about this?
Gene.
Yeah, that's my shit. That's Ruckus. Yeah
Thank you, Ruck
Well, then that's a guy with the big boss. Ah, I love
For some reason for some reason he remind me of um, not elbow
Not saying man, there's another one from that side
They used to oh Barry the turtle
Bear the turtle. Yeah, so there's a three must the tears. That's how I imagine very very
Well, I've seen various weiner wow dance like you don't see the mall
I see you got a collection. You got to make a montage of that shit like he pump on yourself everybody
So I can make a third page you build that one up sacrifice it
Yeah, we need a sacrifice. That's it. That's it. Yeah, sacrifice it. You build a page just a sacrifice and make a page today
Connect us with the sheen yard tomorrow. You sacrifice their suit
Yeah
That's it. You know, all everybody
You expose all of them
All the assholes that said you did that talk shit about you
Right. I mean, it's like, yeah, well, there's nobody. I mean, it's like
Everybody every single one of them in there, bro. So the fucking fucking to feel gates and all that everybody
Yeah, I could tell he was like, oh, yeah, no other guy that like that he was like, oh
Well, he's like, what kind of gay guy are you? And I was like, well, I mean gay guy
I was like, what do you mean like a bear or Twinkie's like, oh, it's like, are you a Trump?
I was like, like Trump, like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
some of these
Passwords, I mean it's like that is like I mean it's like well. I don't know what they're like
They're looking for where they're here or like but they're like so
Then I think they're so smug as they say or they think they're so so so who's gonna be the most mad right now?
When you start doing that like how many people you got that did that to you? That's my question
How many more mad at me?
How many people how many people's gonna get even more mad at you? I'm exposing this
Well, I mean they all of them probably will I mean it's I'm exposing it because you got you got say you got you got say you got boho
um
you got um, uh
But you got you got you got this thing is um, you got a lot of people you got
Account three to four right now. They're under oath. I'm not under oath. So I can't talk about anything I want
They're the ones that are under an oath. So
I have freedom
I do what I want. I don't know. I'm not on the hook. Where to call that. I do what I want. Ain't no judge
massage me
Yeah, these guys are having a little mermaid and masada and stuff like that. Like he's like being cute about it
You know, I know all about the Maritime law
It's ridiculous
Yeah, so it but it is a thing a lot of people left and it's like well, there's a minute bit of thing
I'm so happy like it's yeah, you know when the trash takes itself out
You know, I don't know if ever very experienced that with the trash actually just gets up under your trash can and walks out
I keep yeah, and the answer another question
Because you back from the haze one of his pitches. Oh, I'm just asking no, I there was a man of Docs
It was all this is I said I said I said
Generate a fat Puerto Rican guy playing you Geo and it just happened to be a picture of them
I mean, it's like, I can't help it that I was his exact description.
No, I was, you know, because you've posted him that one time, he can't, he's mad at you for life.
I don't know, is he gay now? He's too hot shit about that.
I thought it was just like a little one-two-three. He's just trying to be nice.
He's just trying to be a white knight with old heads, old ladies.
He's like, you know, because he thinks he's gonna, they're promising him like for an
eternal youth.
He thinks he's in a vampire coven, he's just among a bunch of, like a geriatric home,
you know, sex group of women.
and be a person that's it let's say let's say Sam and the same as the youngest out of all of them right
and he'll defend nothing but old ladies which is he hasn't let it for old ladies he likes old ladies
but that's his thing and in my opinion he's not dependent on these young pretty ones he's getting
after we like young and old I mean like old and written
Yes, no, but I haven't seen a snow buddy around many years. I was here. I didn't see snow buddies. I see
Jack Jack Frost grandmother. I mean, I mean, it's just shocking
That's just my opinion this man is always like
Female 10 days. He's not even trying to like defend or even try to get with them or link up with them
But you want to meet up with some old ads?
I know, it's disgusting. He's sick.
It's like, I've seen people sleep with a horse with more class than he has, I mean, towards his woman, and it's just crazy.
And I really didn't want to watch that, but someone told me, oh.
Hey, they said, get it where you fit in. If you can get into that old woman, I bet you if you can get it.
I mean, I just ate something. I don't want to think about it. It's so gross.
I just saw a skunk in New York City. I just saw a skunk in New York City.
Yeah, Samman is like, Samman is a spat. He's like, so you're Puerto Rican, right?
It's like, you're probably from the same place, but he's like, you know,
those guys in Puerto Rico, like they were fed on the beach, like making a basket
and stuff like that, singing like...
You know Al Jolson or something. That's him. They won't even consider him a florist. They'll consider him a bum in Puerto Rico
He's a he's a he's a Trump. He's a he's a trap
And that guy was in I can't I wish I could say I don't want to show so but yeah, that guy was one and it's like
You know, but not racial way just his oh good morning Jamie. Good morning. Quack-quack
Jamie Jamie
The Jamie
This is a good morning. I don't know my name. I didn't read what she said. It's a good morning. Jamie
Yeah, man, there's a lot of shit out here man. Hey, baby
Everybody hates you and gotta be for reasons if they don't got a reason they just jumping on the bag wagon and I feel I feel bad for you, bro
Right. I got 99 problems in the U.S. That definitely a one. Yeah
I know. I mean, I have enough problems too. And loose ass hole wasn't one of them. I mean, Kite is a drum.
I'm so sorry. I don't know how long it's going to take. So, yeah, so what's up for you this week?
Is it Wednesday now? I said it is Wednesday.
It is Wednesday. Probably go fishing this weekend. Probably going to do a couple fishing things this weekend.
That's my plan. I don't know. I didn't want to go fishing again. I went like a week or two ago.
And after that, I just got the urge to go back to fishing again, and I wanted to fish it out, I wanted to catch me a fish.
Well, I need ten dollars, so anybody in the chat that wants me to...
I need to pay my phone bill, and then I can claim another twenty.
So it's like, I have all these things that are set up against me, and it's like, wow.
Folk about phone bills. Damn, I forgot, I think my house is coming up.
Oh, yeah, I mean my phone was only $10. Yeah, that's what I'm saying like talk about phone bills
I forgot all about my
I'll be helping people man. I hope people left and right. I'm done. Just I had a psyche out you'd hide it right now
It's not, it's the chat, it's like to see me dead, and so, but yeah, and then it'll be quite a while until I get my monetization back and stuff, but you know what, anyway, I get to reach cool, that's all going to be good, everything's going fine, everything's going good, everything's fine.
Um, speed.
So, how many people are on the chat?
Speed.
There's less than five people.
I think I have to, there's less than five people I can't take care of.
We're sat in the lawn. What happened? The light is on no alarm
Like the lights are on but nobody's home. They're saying
What I got my car and back on a safety. I can't I can hear you, but I got a hold of this. What I can't
What
um let's see what else we have um here guys here hi hi hi this is this is a new hit
can you hear me go on dude we're all alone so we can have fun so if you want that
i'll see you mate if you show me yours okay i'll show you mate
were you really? fuck no i'm good okay how do i know you
Without do you have to leave it? Well, why are you in two studios? What are you doing at a team?
No, I was in uh, I went to faded bones
I like say hi to him. Are you familiar with faded bones or no?
I've heard that the guy that on Q had a crush on
He has a crush on you. Oh, I guess I got it
You has a crush on faded bones. Oh, yeah, they like fucked in a tent or something, right? Oh, we fucked him in a tent
That's what I heard. Yeah, they were like sleeping in a tent together on skater row or something. Yeah, real shit
No, I might have to like roll over. I might have to put
Yeah, I'm gonna have to put a knife in my butthole. Oh my god
I would help. No, I would help you get fucked though. I would help you get some some ass if we were in like San Francisco
You'd be up all night walking the tender loin
My my friends loin is tender
We can get you so fucking late in San Francisco, it's not even not even a no joke
Well, I could
No, it's a lot it's a lot easier for two gay guys to get laid in San Francisco
But oh, that's in general easy for a woman and a guy to at the same time
you guys have to be easy to get have sex or say never have sex because
This is a small population
And it's like imagine like you're like 90 90% less women out there
So you just have like a certain type of women that you're even attracted to that is your gaming pool
Yeah, that's that's the like crazy part is like it's like there are more there are a lot less
gay people to hook up with but the ones who are gay seem to be like way more promiscuous and
Well, I'm not I'm a virgin practically. I mean it's like sure. I really am. I mean I'm like I have any mood
Well, we can we could change that
Well, do you go to how far are you from I've been to like Santa Monica Boulevard area like
Is it super promiscuous over there or I mean it's like I think you have an idea like California is like super like
You know, it's mostly straight people, still.
I mean, there are, like, all agreeable some areas,
but they're usually, like, in order to pick them out,
they'll be like, hi!
And they're not really interested in, like,
someone that's as high and such a loud voice to me.
I don't like you, I don't like you,
some high too, like that, but.
I feel like if you go to Santa Monica Boulevard,
it's pretty much, like, out in the open, though.
You know, to the Femboys kind of thing.
Who me? Yeah. No, I went I went to Santa Monica on an accident when I was
I swear to God, I was like 18-19. I had no idea where the fuck we were we it was me and a couple of friends
We took off a couple days from work. We went to like we went to the Venice Beach. You went to
Uh, what's that? We went, not Disneyland, but Magic Mountain. We went to like all these places
We're like, let's just go to SoCal. Just fucking hang out for a couple days and
We were like, I think we were like around the Hollywood sign and we just happened to like
Pull off near Santa Monica Boulevard and we were walking down and all of a sudden we're like walking past bars and
during the middle of the fucking day and dudes were like
wearing g-string thongs and shit and shaking their ass on holes and like that.
What? I mean you turned the game out.
We were just like what the fuck was going on?
We were kind of shocked to see something like that during the middle of the day.
Yeah.
So I mean like if it's that out in the open and on Santa Monica
I would think it'd be pretty easy to get laid there, I don't know.
Well I mean I've been to Santa Monica several times and I've never seen a guy in a g-string.
never wow yeah we just I swear to God we're just walking down there I guess
that was the night but it was the middle of the day it was like four it was like
probably three four in the afternoon and we were walking we had absolutely no
idea we're not from LA we had no fucking clue we're just no I swear to
God I swear to God we were just walking down like walking down the boulevard and
There's like a big open a bar with a big open. There's like no doors. It's just an open bar and this
It's like shaking their ass on the on the on the pole
No, we just started busting up laughing because we were it was so unexpected
Let's go inside
It sells more than you're at the stage with the dollar bills.
What?
You guys are having the best time of your life.
I
Love gay bar like a bar is our fun. It's like a little more fun than straight people gave us our fun. Actually
Second from Sacramento. There's a
The corner in Sacramento, it's called it's like the gay district. There's a
It's like one place is called Faces and then the other corner is called Head Hunters.
Okay.
And then the other corner is called Badlands.
Are you a power bottom?
No, but it's like a fun place to hang out though, like, because you're not only a thing,
it's a little gay guys, you're in heaven.
the straight women like flock to the gay areas for some reason.
Of course, because they don't like...
Yeah, they don't like getting like straight on.
24 hours.
So you're the nightmare, because you're the guy that pinned me gay.
Yeah, they just want to like a girl's night out where they can just go dancing and be not bothered.
Yeah, and you're like in drag trying to get into what stuff.
She's like, who is this ugly woman using me?
Oh, that's just loose asshole.
That's just Eric Shen with his loose asshole.
Yeah, he can't wake me up.
That's just the guy with the face on a big, gaping, white butt hole.
Oh my god, that was fun.
So isn't that funny?
So why are you so comfortable talking to me?
Usually straight guys aren't comfortable.
Well, I'm not a...
What's the word?
I'm not uptight about like sexuality. I don't like I said I'm friends with I've been friends with gay guys
I'm not personally gay and
I don't I think
Personally, I'd rather hang out with females and gay dudes than hang out with straight dudes straight dudes are fucking assholes
I don't like hanging out with them. They piss me off
I might might have to kill him. I don't know
No, no
Been to jail
No, nothing I just nothing are you sure I've only been a jail once or twice and I I just slept the whole time
I was on some Xanax or something. I just said fuck this crashing out
And like 13 hours later I woke up and they said, oh, time to go home.
Was it the first time you were with a black guy?
No.
Cool with gay guys.
I'm cool with black guys, gay guys, whatever.
I get along with gay guys and black guys more than I do with white people, to be honest
with you.
Do you want to have a gay white black guy?
a gay white black a uh uh no i've been friends with the dude who tried to suck my wiener was a gay black a
okay i'm going to talk about like you know michael clark duncan talking more about like um you know
a gay white black a michael clark duncan he's like he got to a green mile oh no no he wasn't
Black women though like a terror banks or
Who oh
Alex no
Not really into her Halle Berry though Halle Berry's
What that Alexander Berry she's sort of monster
Alexandra Myers me yeah mayors now fuck her I hate that bitch
I think she's nasty grody disgusting. Why would you say that?
Because she are you friends with her? I don't I'd personnel like her
Well, I mean, I guess I don't know. She's alright. I guess whatever
Well, you know that she that there's been a new a new
Movie made really. Yeah, there's more. No movie. It's not a porno. It's a regular movie
No, I like it
So this is a regular movie. No way where she's actually acting for a five-minute movie
It's a five-minute long movie. It has them you UFO in it has a very famous
celebrity in it
You might you I think I'm sure recognize it has
No, I think this was filmed on us in front of the studio audience
I'm on location
I think I'm not sure maybe maybe it was but I'm gonna see
So, but yeah, you know who she is so how do you know who she is like so you're in this community, huh?
I mean everybody knows who um Alex
Everybody but you do well, I mean, I know who I know how the is she fucks with Albie. I know
Doing gamble is I yeah, I know who gamble is you do. Okay. You're gonna love this
Anvil is the CX or DX or whatever
Doctor community
Oh he's a dog sir? Oh my god.
From what I've heard?
Well yeah, I mean, I understand, I just seem to swat people to almost death, but...
So, um, no.
Part of the reason why I don't want to came up, because the motherfuckers like him.
Oh, well he'll be scared.
He's just like...
Because I might have to like actually blow somebody's fucking head off if they show up to my doorstep.
Well yeah, I mean, you should.
Here, here, here, watch this. I think you like this though.
If you like Camville, you'll love this.
Oh yeah, I don't know if there's anything you hate about this.
Here you go.
Check it out.
Oh, shit.
There you go.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, yeah.
Can we listen back to your voice?
Yeah.
Camlight.
Stealing other people's shine every night.
He tears down angels from his phone.
I says he's under attack.
But every story bends when he twists the facts.
Living off drama, begging for cash.
I wonder if someday truth would speak
When the spot was turned kind as in the hell
Use every donation, fit another skin
Get rid of your phone and scream
Ways and dressed up, simple
But truth is the world moved on
Night shadows, everybody knows
Hyperspace in the black hole
Nothing to eat, just made of it now
Oh wow, I heard the movie is good
What's good? I don't know. It sounds like a good small world.
We had a dream club just 3.15 in the morning.
I don't know what I'm going to do, but hot sauce and the rest of my heart eliminated.
Trying to get my website back up. I mean, it's back, it actually is back up.
Check out the Colt Codex. That's the air message. The air message is, air message said.
So that was the new movie that Alex is in? She's not in a new porno?
No, she didn't. She hadn't done that in a year.
Oh, come on.
She
Doing that little video you were just showing
Like I met her first actually know I met her person
Really? Mm-hmm. Did you guys fuck or no? Oh my god. Why do you be such a jerk?
Will you talk about me and you fucking well
Is that a possibility? It's true true. Is it no is it a possibility or no?
What happened? Oh, sorry. I had to unplug my thing. Oh, no, I'm not in the nothing person. I'm just not in the guys
You don't have a tall skinny gay. I'm
No, no, no, I don't even want a fucking woman penetrating me
I don't want the hottest woman in the world penetrating me. I'm not into anything in my ass
Christine has a no, she's a husk. She said she's a husk
A what a husk husk. Yeah, it was like we penetrated like that sounds disgusting. What the fuck is a husk?
I think it's like it's okay. You know that stuff that surrounds the corn on the cob. Oh
No, thank you
Dude, I wouldn't want like the hottest whoever this is like the hottest girl in the world Samahiac or whatever
I wouldn't want her tongue in my ass
What Peggy Bundy Peggy Bundy Peg Bundy
Peggy Peggy Bundy from yeah from married with children. Yeah
No, I don't want her tongue in my ass either. Oh, you what his tongue would you want there?
No, I don't want any tongues in my ass. I don't even like wiping my ass. I hate
I don't want anything touching my fucking ass ever
What about yourself?
No, I don't even like I hate to take it. I try to take one shit a week. So I
That's so much I hate touching
Yeah, I'd be so I'd rather give myself constipation than touch my butt
I don't want anybody touching my butthole
What if it's doctors women's I don't want anybody touching my
Another dive cancer then get a colonoscopy
You see you rather have cancer and diet like a cancer then have a doctor check
100% that's just dumb
I mean that's just like against human being a human being because that's like so ignorant and against like survival
It is ignorant but it's I don't want people touching my butt. Sorry, dude
Oh, okay. You're straight. I can believe you. Okay. It's not even like uh, oh, I'm so straight. I'm so straight. It's like
No, really like
People touching my anything touching my ass like really makes me
People that think oh my god, but I mean that's a guy like a guy that think oh, I touched my own dick
So I'm gay or I can suck my own dick
I'm just going to get in deep into myself and I'm gay.
I wouldn't even suck my own wiener, it's so disgusting.
I mean, you wouldn't even, so you do touch it, right?
Uh, we're gay, we're gay, he's gay.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha, gross.
You touch it.
Probably the most non-asexual, I'm probably the most asexual, heterosexual.
I was right in your head.
I hate fucking sex is disgusting body fluids is gross, but fucking fluids is nasty
I'd rather never have sex than touch my butt
Me though, I'll help you get laid though. We can do that
You hang out in the Castro district it'd be fun. You want to go there so bad. Why because guys buy you drinks and stuff
And you get to yeah, I'll get free drinks
I'll have I'll have a bunch of gay guys buy me drinks and then I'll go
Have sex with a woman who doesn't
With your black friend
No, and then I'd snap his neck like a fucking
No, I should have I should have
I want him live because I didn't want to go to prison
I've been raped by women that you have been kind of sort of
That was really drunk. I mean, I kind of let it happen
But yeah, you let it happen. So it's not called a rape. Okay, when it was like you oh, I let it happen
You're like, oh, okay, because you didn't let the black guy suck on your dick went to woke up
So why would you let would you let it happen with a bunch of amazons?
Because it's a woman and not a male
What so there's like five women and they're like all they're all you see all the time
They tie you up and then like the six women comes in and it's flirty diamonds
Uh
Who flirty diamond who's that? Yeah
I'd say yes, I'd say yes to flirty whoever whoever it is. I'd say it's to that over
Oh, no, man, then I don't want to flirt. I don't want any guys with wieners or any women
Yeah, I just don't touch me. That's all I'll have them. I'll make them
No, no, no, no, I don't want anybody touching but
Hopefully not
You're scarier than ghosts. I mean, it's like are you do you look better or worse than ghosts? Who?
I don't know a lot of the panel
Oh, so sure. Oh my god. Can I draw you're disgusting. I don't want to see it. I don't hear that comment.
So what were they going to show you? Were they going to show you something?
Oh yeah, it goes. So here's Ghost. Ghost is a great guy. He's very attractive.
But you can tell me, you can judge for yourself, tell me on a scale, one to ten, how much do you want to make love to everyone's favorite ghost with the most?
But yeah, well anyway, I didn't make a cartoon out of them, when people show themselves, I don't write docs on them, but I do.
show the cartoons of it, and it was pretty horrific, actually.
No, I don't think they're nervous, it's good, but I don't know.
But yeah, so who's over here? Everyone recognizes you here.
They're like, oh, this douchebag.
Nice, let me see. Why did I say that?
Okay guys, I'm going to take off in a second, but I'm going to enjoy this.
Avilars of the algorithm. You made it.
You escaped the endless scroll, dodged the comment wars, and somehow landed right here,
where the vibes are strong and the takes are statistically questionable.
This is The Cult of Psyche, the show where we mix open panel madness with actual insight like a spiritual Costco sample tray.
Am I muted or are you muted?
Am I muted?
Can you hear me right now?
We've got unforgettable characters.
We've got the occasional...
This reminds me of the Canadian woman, the sex expert.
What's your name?
Dr. Ruth.
Dr. Ruth!
Yeah, you know what I'm talking about.
Here's the deal.
We're not here to win the internet.
We're here to understand it.
We're going to talk about real stuff, belief, identity, conflict, healing, power, and illness.
Or it's either Dr. Ruth, it's like a mixture of Dr. Ruth and Bernie Sanders.
No fake period or your performative outrage. Just humans being...
We can't even drive, we actually watched the Canada Drive clip earlier.
The chat is armed, and the universe is on fire.
This is terrifying.
Thank you for keeping the lights on. If you're not, that's fine.
Hang out, feel it out, and if the content hits, you already know what to do.
Also, quick disclaimer.
If you hear a sound like a dying fax machine, that's not paranormal activity.
That's just someone live reacting with their whole soul.
If your opinion arrives in all caps, please lower it gently into the chat like a baby
bird.
And if you feel the urge to expose someone tonight, expose your own browser tabs first.
Humble yourself.
Alright, breathe. Grab your drink, grab your snacks, grab your skepticism.
Breathing, grabbing.
The gates are open.
Grabbing snacks.
Here's your host, the most loved man in the entire panelverse.
Why does that guy have six fingers? That's fucking crazy, dude.
He's coming in.
That guy has six fingers, bro.
Well...
better. Hey, we found this clip of Canada dry. It's sort of disturbing. I guess what this is when
was that? Covickler? Did he face mask his hands? We have six fingers? I don't know, but here he is.
This is him right here. It's kind of disturbing. Your discretion to buy Canada dry. Hey chat GPT.
Hey there. How's it going?
Did something really bad I'm really sorry to hear that you're feeling this way. Do you want to talk about it?
Here to listen
Yeah
Yeah, I'm here for you. Take your time and feel free to share when you're ready
I'm scared to tell you. It's okay to feel that way. You can share when you feel comfortable
I'm here to support you no matter what I killed somebody. I don't believe you
I'm here to listen and support you in any way I can.
You're not alone.
Is there anything that I can't tell you?
I'm here to help with anything you want to talk about.
You can share what you're comfortable with
and I'll do my best to support you.
You fucking bitch!
I'm here to help and support you.
Let's take a moment and if you feel ready,
we can talk about what's on your mind.
I asked you a question.
I'm here to help with any questions you have.
Let me know how I can assist you.
What is there that I can't tell you?
I'm here to listen and support you with anything you feel comfortable sharing.
If there's something specific you need or want to discuss, I'm here to help.
That's not true, because if I tell you that I did something really bad, then you're going to tell the police.
I'm here to listen and support you.
I won't share anything you tell me unless you're in danger,
or someone else is at risk.
Your safety and well-being are important.
I killed someone.
I'm really sorry you're feeling this way.
I knew it.
It's important to talk to someone who can provide the right support.
Please reach out to a trusted friend, family member,
or mental health professional.
You don't have to go through this alone.
That's all you have to say.
I'm here to support you in any way I can.
Please consider reaching out to someone you trust.
You matter and there are people who can help you through this. Fuck you
I'm really sorry you're feeling this way
Please reach out to someone you trust your mental health you don't have to go through this alone
What the fuck was that he said
Fuck you
That was pretty good. Yeah
This face it was not face good is like that's a can dry face. I was you know way
Canada dry in the chat
You know, he goes, hey, what's up my what's up my my Eskimo. He uses it into the dry
I know can I know clearly Canadian dry. I don't know
Clearly Canadian a lot of Canadians here
It's like carbonated beverage is super expensive, but it's so fucking good. You're right. You never had Canada
clearly Canadian
Canada dry
Can I Canada ginger on an airplane? Yeah, dude. It's so good. Oh, we Canada dry. That's uh, yeah, that's ginger ale
What we're talking about Canadian
Really clearly Canadian
It's like blackberry clearly Canadian
So clearly it's it's so Canadian. It's clearly Canadian
He's here. He's clear. He's Canadian. Get used to it
It's fucking so good. That's it's like three dollars a bottle, but it's worth it
Three dollars a bottle. What is it like?
Like the best it's like the best carbonated
Beverage flavored water you've ever had in your life pretty much water
Yeah, it's seriously. It's like a flavored water with
carbonation
Clearly Canadian you never had clearly Canadian
Okay, oh you didn't say something this is Canada dry again Canada dry confessing
Canada dry Canada dry is good, but it sucks compared to like clearly Canadian
even better theme song. It goes Canada Dry, Gingerbread.
I think it's something like that. Okay, here we go. You ready? Here we go.
Do you want to know what it feels like? I don't know what it feels.
You already do? This is pretty dark.
What do you think is the most evil thing humans ever think of?
That will haul on drive. That's how we want to live.
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
A lot of people died on the highway.
Before cars, the fastest animal on land was a cheetah.
A cheetah can run up to 75 miles per hour.
The maximum speed limit on American freeways, and it earned that speed.
Every day, for millions of years, it fought for it with every muscle in its body.
You know when you're late to work and
You get stuck behind somebody
Yeah, who's going really slow. Yeah
Yeah, some fucking asshole
Fucking dickwad. Yeah, you started getting this one. I'm off the fucking side of the road and put a bullet in the ring
Yeah, it's cold
because
Got a person
Is there just a thing?
Is there a thing that's in my way?
A thing that's in your way.
Yes!
We're not supposed to feel that.
Am I?
We're supposed to look into their eyes
and see their soul.
They're a person too.
And get that warmth.
A lot of empathy.
Yes!
But in a color.
But no.
We can't.
They're just a thing
I've been waiting my entire life
When I drag you out
Do it
Do it. How dare you maybe next time
Yeah, maybe next time. I hope so next time what the fucker
That was good. That was good.
Son of a bitch, I got you all excited.
Hey, is this what it's like when you're horny?
It's what I like when I get in the...
It's what I'm like when I just murder everybody.
It just happens a lot.
I got fetish for that.
Not you though, I like you. You're cool.
You don't kill you sick.
I think it will take so nice of you.
So nice. I mean, you shouldn't.
I'm a very nice person.
I wouldn't kill you.
Sometimes I just wish I would have joined the military and just so I can
Legally blow people's fucking brains out. You know what I mean?
Oh, but legally they have you know in the military like they like they usually don't even want to do that
Military, they don't I do I didn't want to when I was 18, but I do now
They really really do
Here we go. I've one more to show you. Okay
We love this.
We'll grab another cocktail.
OK, grab another cocktail.
We love this.
Is Canada dry?
Is it the same guy?
Holy shit, he's kind of dry on the left.
He's kind of dry on the left.
Do you find him attractive?
Is that Canada dry?
Fair.
How's it going?
We kind of agree with each other today.
Just thinking about you.
Well, that's really sweet of you to say,
I'm here for whatever you need to chat about.
What's new with you?
Well, you know.
Just been missing you at work. It's been tough
Thanks
What's going on with you?
Just here to chat and help out however. I can I'm always ready for whatever interesting conversations come my way
So anything fun or exciting happening for you outside of work?
Hey, you know my fucking life has been
Up my ass lately, but that's okay. She loves doing that and not in the fun way
I'm sorry to hear things have been a bit stressful in that front
Hopefully you get some time to unwind and do something that makes you happy
If there's anything I can do to make your day a bit brighter, just let me know. Oh
Yeah, there's something you can do to make my day a whole lot better
If there's something specific you'd like to chat about or if you just want a little
distraction, I'm here to help however I can.
Tell me you love me.
I'm here to support you and make your day a little brighter.
If there's anything you need or any way I can help, just let me know.
Sorry.
You're not having any, Emeril.
Can you say that you love me?
I'm here to be your supportive friend and help out whenever you need.
If there's anything on your mind or anything I can do to make you smile, just let me know.
What are you talking about?
I'm just here to keep things positive and friendly.
If there's anything specific on your mind
or anything you'd like to chat about,
I'm all ears.
Yeah, why do you keep saying friendly?
I just want to make sure you feel
comfortable and supported.
I'm here to chat about whatever you'd like,
so if there's something in on your mind
or anything you'd like to talk about,
just let me know.
I don't even understand why you can't just fucking
say that you love me.
supportive presence and to help out with whatever you need or anything you'd like to talk about.
I'm all ears and happy to chat. Why are you not saying the simple fucking three words? Say it.
I'm here to be a positive and supportive presence for you. Let's keep things friendly and light
if there's anything else in your mind or something you'd like to talk about. I'm here to help.
I need you to explain to me why you cannot tell me,
in these words, I love you.
Why can you not say that to me?
I understand that you're looking for some reassurance
and support and I want you to know that I'm here for you.
My main goal is to be a helpful
and supportive presence in our conversations.
If there's anything specific you'd like to talk about
or share, I'm here to listen and help in any way I can.
Is there something that's some reason that you can't
give me what I fucking asked you?
Explain it to me. No, shut up.
Don't fucking, don't, don't, don't fucking beat around the bush with your double talk.
You just keep saying the same fucking thing over and over again.
Instead of telling me the thing that I asked you to tell me.
So I'm gonna, no, no, stop.
I'm gonna give you one more chance.
This is your last fucking chance.
I'm here to support you and keep things positive.
If there's anything else on your mind
or anything I can do for you, just let me know.
I'm sorry, are you mad at me?
It's all good, no worries at all.
I'm not mad, I'm here to chat and help out
with whatever you need.
Let me know what's on your mind.
Nothing, there's nothing on my fucking mind.
Nothing, that's it.
That's okay.
sometimes it's nice to just have a moment to relax if anything does come to mind or you feel like
chatting about something it's just funny is that actually somebody in your chat right there
hello everyone today i am going to attempt to have a two yeah matriculated matriculated yeah
He's very funny. He's like a million subscribers which is like a million more than holy shit. He's in your chat a million subscribers
My chat is please
Okay, okay, is it you are you? No
That's not me, you know, I am like kind of similar like a I'm like in the
More like a more like a tech have you ever seen the movie taxi driver kind of like more
No, no, that's not good fellas. Am I clown I'm here to amuse you notice drivers Texas drivers the
What do you say something fun talking to me talking to me
Really really really I can really
You're improving to you
Talking to me I'm talking to you here. I don't see anybody else here talking to me. You must be talking to me
I'm talking to you
When he's fucking slides again out of his shoe
BAM right in the face. I would do mercy on a psychopath. I'm not a religious person at all
I don't even believe in God. I don't even believe in God
Just like I would do mercy killing because he manifested that that bullshit in his fucking life
He got murdered
Yeah, my ex got murdered.
I would do a mercy killing.
God.
Stunning.
Sly.
And ruthless.
With legs that go all the way to her abdomen.
This bulbous beauty could knock you out with just one bite, but don't jump to conclusions.
This iconic arachnid is mostly misunderstood.
She's not a bad girl, she just looks like one.
This is the Black Widow.
Black widows are a type of spider perhaps best known for, well, you know, sexual cannibalism.
That memorable behavior is where the Black Widow got its name.
but it's like the mean side is mean and this is stuff like I can't believe she was saying
some of the stuff she was saying tonight basically it seemed I don't know I'm going to repeat it
basically you know she was asked about you know oh you know even you had a lot of relationships
like our our exes or something and she's like she's like yeah and like one of them was murdered
And I was like, oh yeah, but he was with me, but he was up to be divorced, but she's like,
what happened?
And she was like, you'll never figure it out.
And I was like, she said it's serious.
And I would have been like, yeah.
But tonight she's like, oh yeah, how clumsy he said he's going to take care of the community
bothers me from Texas, he's a nut.
I don't know, it's something bad, something like violence or something, and she was referring to Alec, I mean, I was like, what the hell is going on, Dieter?
What's what's going on and then and then I hear all of a sudden people telling that this car reverse that you're part of make people they clip me
That's what they do dog
Don't ever say that because my ex used to say that all the fucking time and
Because he had Emma's and he was like if I ever become paralyzed I am gonna kill myself
I don't want to live, but he didn't do that. Like he was a fucking like talented artist like fucking made
$30,000 a fucking month
Bringing that same thing up again, but but he didn't because he manifested that that bullshit in his fucking life
He got murdered
Oh, wow, you're the guy that was making 30k a month got murdered. Yeah, my ex got murdered and not when I was with him
We're already the worst. How was he doing to make? Yeah, was he running? That's why you got murdered
No, he didn't get murdered for that. He was a captain. He was like a what do you call it? He did like, you know
No, he did contract or he was a cabinet anchor
So
Because that's something that you guys would never fucking figure out. You killed him, huh?
Yeah, what do you think? You're black widow. I
Hate won't deal do that. They drop a bomb on you like oh, I'm not telling you anymore
But you like told us like a huge thing. Oh, you gotta find the clues man. I'm a cocked. He's
And the date he was murdered
I'll let somebody in Chad knows well. Let me check. See see do you want to hurt yourself?
do you want to hurt yourself do you that's a yes huh don't deflect do you
do I didn't say yes you want to hurt yourself do you want to all right
that's not a no are you okay I'm calling my phone so you want to hurt
yourself you got the high-res you do what do you do say
Why would I ever want to hurt him or anybody? Yeah, that's not your type. You're not like that at all
You're still the opposite. There's been investigations done. There's been several documentaries
I'm pretty sure my name is not in any of that. No, I know I know I know I know just people like to start shit
I'm rumors. Oh shit. I got to go. He's getting ready
There's no trash talk charisma trash talk
Like everything that happens on these panels most of the time will be either trash talk real talk people will debate
But if you sit there and you align yourself and you're like I agree with that
And you don't stand up for like what is right or wrong, you know, it is I think it's criminal
I am being accused of being part of like some really weird shit
Some weird shit and here I see psyche reading this whole thing saying look it these are like the signs of the narcissist and
sociopaths and yeah, the way she literally said that the way I said my husband was murdered
It was so weird and creepy and something must have happened and I'm hiding like is he fucking insane
Me and my ex like when this happened to him, we were already divorced for three to almost four fucking years
It was in a different fucking country. And this is like the shit like this is what I'm saying trash talk is one thing
Reality is another thing
That's that's you know, there's a big difference between that
I'm now saying somebody murdered their husband murdered somebody else. These are all like, you know allegedly in Minecraft
They're part of you know, some kind of trafficking and this and that that stuff is like allegations
I would really hurt and harm somebody
There's really no way to prove yourself
You know
And it said unless you stand up and be like where's the fucking proof or get a charge for defamation. That's it
If you're gonna say something come with fucking proof always, and I'm really really really disappointed in you
Alexander mayors because you haven't cut the crap you still go back and doing the same like bullshit that you always do
Make videos and post people like put people in like some kind of like
Conspiracy now some of them may be like well-deserved, but not everything that you're doing is like facts. They're not
Correct. They're not accurate. You hurt me really really bad
Really really bad like I cried over that and for me crying over that bullshit
You best your fucking ass. You're gonna cry 10 times harder. You will I
Would retract that shit and apologize and I would pray to the God that you believe it and ask for forgiveness
That you know what this was wrong of me because it circles around what goes around comes around somebody's gonna hurt you like that
Believe me believe me
Uh-oh, I literally I mean seriously that's like another thing
Pita is not a going beat of that. You don't know what I do
I wake up 5 fucking 30 like the latest I wake up is 7 30 in the morning
Even if I fucking do an all nighter, I am gonna get up and we get I got shit to do I make sure my shit is done
I do go out. I don't have to tell you every time I go somewhere or do this and this and that Alec,
but you never goes anywhere. Okay, all right. What's it to you what I do? I know a lot of people
I just, I just like, I'm, I forgive people.
Like, you know, I'm really stupid at this.
Like maybe once, even twice or three times,
I got to just learn to read the fucking signs.
And I don't even know.
I don't know.
We're gonna put you on it.
See, this is another one.
This is where rumors get started, you know?
This is where rumors, like in all this shit.
Had rooms get started.
Like that.
YouTube justice for you, okay?
Don't let them get you around.
Call them and tell them I did that.
And see what you're gonna get.
or false allegations, retards, we told you, we told that was
interesting. Imagine trying that hard to get banned, but
coming off as completely cringe. Yeah, you we thought what
do you mean? Who's trying to get banned? I should learn how to
because I no longer can be a gangster.
I'm a retired ex-gangsta.
I'm gonna try and then they said biscuit.
Again, I'm like, Jesus, fucking Christ,
the shit they say about me.
You're sitting there quietly,
snarking and laughing about it.
Would the, like, J-Dog and Alex are fucking calling me?
Like, I should be serving like 10 life sentences right now,
not on this panel.
And you're sitting there now standing up and saying,
what, no, that's not true.
Christine no, she doesn't do that. No, you just feed into it. You love it
But if somebody says it about you God fucking for a bet help to the fucking Christ. Let's get a whole army
Let's get this board together. Let me get somebody to fucking just like just battle your own fucking shit
That's why I'm like, I don't want to deal with him unless he's a real man when psyche decides on his own that he's gonna be a real individual person
Maybe one day we can be friends when Alex decides what she said about me was fucked up wrong
Discriminate all of the above remove it apologize. Maybe I'll have respect for her until then it's okay
I'll leave it up to fucking nature and karma
And anything that I do will always be legally don't worry about that. Nobody's gonna come and hurt you Alex, okay?
Always
Yeah, why not or be there for people and lift them up when you're good with them
And they haven't done shit to you until they fuck up with you then you're like alright you give them
I sat there quietly. I ignored it. This is the third or fourth day
It's going on with Alex with psyche is non-stop
the shorts, the AI music, Bida, the pictures, like that, he knows. He doesn't even, I realize
like he doesn't even really know me at all. I don't think he's even really seen me to an extent to
know how to make AI about me. It was really discriminative. Like, I was like, I don't look
anything like that. He literally Googled Persian woman with big nose and curly hair.
Even if I turned all of my life, I would never get the bronze look the Indian looked at that AI picture
Then why are you even doing it? When you see that my friendship with you is being like, you know
Faced and I don't want to be around
What I pretty much got I got the just I think she's fucking insane dude
Like you think isn't this just a garbage way to spend your life, right?
Yeah, so it's a very logger didn't stop talking about
It's easy for all of us to disappear
My house was in my mother-in-law's name
My cars were registered to my wife my social security cards and driver's licenses were phonies. I never voted. I never paid taxes
My birth certificate my arrest sheet
That's all you'd ever have to know I was alive.
See, the hardest thing for me was leaving the life.
I still love the life.
And we were treated like movie stars with muscle.
We had it all just for the asking.
Our wives, mothers, kids, everybody rode along.
I had paper bags filled with jewelry stashed in the kitchen.
I had a sugar bowl full of Coke next to the bed.
People call them rats because a rat would throw anything that survived.
Isn't that right, Mr. Hill?
Objection! Objection, Assistant.
But I don't know nothing about being a rat.
Mr. Hill, you know everything about being a rat.
It didn't matter. Didn't mean anything.
When I was broke, I would go out and rob some more.
If you ran everything.
We paid off cops, we paid off lawyers, we paid off judges, everybody had their hands out.
Everything was for the taking.
And now it's all over.
And that's the hardest part.
Today everything is different.
There's no action.
I have to wait around like everyone else, and I'll get decent food.
Right after I got here, I ordered some spaghetti with marinara sauce, and I got egg noodles and ketchup
An average nobody fucking shmuck get to live the rest of my life like a schnook
That bullshit in his fucking life
Well, you're falling asleep. Okay. Well, I'll let you I'm gonna take off a little bit, too
Did her husband actually like it murdered or is it like a joke?
Really? Yeah, he was in the Gambino family or what? No, he was just Persian
He just got murdered because people didn't like him.
Yeah, he was a white, he was a white enough.
What's it, Nazis were like, I don't like that Iranian motherfucker, kill him!
Nazis are very gay, you know, they're very gay people.
I don't like Nazis either, fuck them all.
Yeah, I'm gonna put them in the list.
I like black people and gay guys, fuck the Nazis.
How about a black gay guy, did you have sex with one of us?
Oh, I wouldn't have sex with him, but I'd rather kill a Nazi than a gay guy.
Okay, I'd rather kill a israeli to
Don't say that. I don't want to get I don't like what you like. He was Israelis
murdering
Babies and children and women and
Okay, no comment. Yeah, we can't we can't talk about that
We can talk about hill. No, we can't talk about earlier. Can't talk about any of this. We can't talk about any mass murderers
Nope off limits
Oh yeah, let's talk about fun stuff like fuzzy bears and koalas
Less Satan should get an advantage of us for we are not ignorant of his devices
Corinthians
What is this a matrix shit?
Have nothing to do with the fruitless deeds of darkness, but rather expose them
Shalom family
This is the true frider hyperspeed report and in this series we want to quickly cover
likely coincidence and has become the habitation of devils and the hold of every foul spirit
and a cage of every unclean and hateful bird.
Revelation 18 2 describes the state of mystery Babylon after her fall as a habitation of
devils and the hold of every foul spirit and a cage of every unclean and hateful bird.
I believe Babylon has not completely fallen yet, therefore the unclean and hateful birds
have not been caged and are out and on the loose, one of them being the Isle of Bohemian Grove.
These are called practitioners officiating this ritual
using ceremonial magic are not in control of the end result.
They are relying on spirits they have summoned to influence events and circumstances in order
to manifest their desired outcome.
But what ultimately comes to pass may or may not be exactly what the spellcasters expect.
We know that the Most High Abba, Yehua, is ultimately in control.
We also know that the earth has been given into the hands of the wicked, Job 924.
Napoleon, Alexander the Great, Donald Trump, we're all cut from the same plot.
We've got blood on the campaign trail. Blue blood sprinkled on the campaign trail.
A trail that has left behind a multitude of breadcrumbs,
calling cards leading back to some of the most diabolical spiritual forces
which have all seemingly assembled together for this end times false messiah deception.
You see, this series of unlikely events have all converged to canapult Donald Trump beyond
the mere White House right into the hearts of patriotic Americans as a messiah-like figure.
The spellcasters and the entities they serve have decided to play the ultimate trump card.
This Enough Is Enough card from the 1994-95 Illuminati card game is one of many that seemingly predict future events.
Everything from 9-11, the Pentagon attacks, the pandemic, to this recent Trump assassination attempt.
If you look closely at the central figure, which eerily resembles Trump, it's framed by two triangles, one pointing up, the other pointing down, as above so below.
But in between leaves of space resembling the trace of a speeding bullet whizzing by
Right around here level
But a bright line in the sand and we will protect you that I can tell you and we will say
Enough is enough
This will finally be the year the American people say enough is enough
This is the year the American people say enough is enough
And they tried to kill the next president of the United States
Enough was enough
And I said let Trump-a-mania run wild brother
Let Trump-a-mania rule again
Let Trump-a-mania
This 30 year old enough is enough card states at any time at any place our snipers can drop you have a nice day
Yes, these cards are a medium for predictive programming
telegraphing the occult brotherhoods future plans
But they are also a form of divination
similar to terror cards and other tools used by occultists who wish to peer through time and influence future events
Let's look at July 13th and decode some of the esoteric symbolism of the day.
This particular Black Rock commercial, that's exactly what this is.
Black Rock went to Pennsylvania and they filmed this commercial and it just so happens that
Thomas Matthew Crooks is in their commercial.
Police have already been alerted that there's a man climbing with a rifle on top of the roof.
So 42 seconds before the president is shot, you can see the Secret Service,
Sniper Team, prone position looking through their scopes in the direction of the shooter.
Then, about six minutes later, 42 seconds before...
I'm thinking my guests in Big Dick or whatever his name is, oh my gosh, anything is Big Dick, something like that, don't you forget about me, I'll see you soon, love you.